<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="pretty-atom-feed.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>Blog Title</title>
  <subtitle>This is a longer description about your blog.</subtitle>
  <link href="https://example.com/eleventy-base-blog/feed/feed.xml" rel="self" />
  <link href="https://example.com/eleventy-base-blog/" />
  <updated>2024-10-22T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <id>https://example.com/eleventy-base-blog/</id>
  <author>
    <name>Your Name</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Beyond Code</title>
    <link href="https://example.com/eleventy-base-blog/blog/2024-10-23-beyond-code/" />
    <updated>2024-10-22T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://example.com/eleventy-base-blog/blog/2024-10-23-beyond-code/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;One of the reasons I started this blog back in 2003 was to use it as a marketing tool for myself. Personal branding had started to become a thing and blogging scene was about to take off big time. I was fortunate enough to grab on to it and together with other community activities, it worked out well for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Software is still my passion but there are also other interests I pursue. Reading, Cooking, Finance, photography are some of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lately I have been pondering the question of merging my tech and non-tech writings in one place. I am much more than a programmer and those aspects do not get any space online.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A question comes to mind: Why bother writing about them at all? Why not just enjoy non-tech adventures in obscurity? Does the world need to know about them?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First of all, I&#39;m confident that this blog is read only by 2 people. One of them is me and the other I have yet to know about. Secondly, and more importantly &lt;mark&gt;this website exists only to serve me&lt;/mark&gt; If anyone else finds anything useful here then it it incidental and not intentional. It is after all a log of my life which will be of no interest to anyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that thought, I decided to make it more complete by writing about the books I have read, the journeys I have been on (there are not too many), photos I have clicked and a lot more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, tinkering with this website gives me the joy similar to working in the garage with tools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So here it is to a more authentic place which is both about and beyond code. Cheers!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Desk Cleanup 2024</title>
    <link href="https://example.com/eleventy-base-blog/blog/2024-10-02-desk-cleanup/" />
    <updated>2024-10-02T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://example.com/eleventy-base-blog/blog/2024-10-02-desk-cleanup/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Few days ago I bought a monitor stand which came in today. It is a Meatanty Dual Monitor Stand Riser with 2 Drawers, 4 Usb Ports and Charging Pad. Recently I made some ergonomic changes to my working environment like changing to a vertical mouse. Although I do not have RSI yet, but sometimes I feel a little bit of pain in my wrist. Before it gets any worse, I have started making some changes to my environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Getting a monitor stand is part of these ergonomic changes. I noticed that I bend my neck slightly to look at the screen. This may not be the best in long term and with the stand, I see the monitor at my natural eye level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I was setting up the stand, I decided to embark on the quest of cleaning my desk which was slowly turning into a museum of all sorts of useless things. Nothing too revolutionary, just removing the clutter which unnecessarily occupied space and added zero value. At the end I&#39;m proud of my achievement. Here is the obligatory photo of what it looks like as I&#39;m writing this post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;picture&gt;&lt;source type=&quot;image/avif&quot; srcset=&quot;https://example.com/eleventy-base-blog/blog/2024-10-02-desk-cleanup/I6UCUSvtsj-4000.avif 4000w&quot;&gt;&lt;source type=&quot;image/webp&quot; srcset=&quot;https://example.com/eleventy-base-blog/blog/2024-10-02-desk-cleanup/I6UCUSvtsj-4000.webp 4000w&quot;&gt;&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; decoding=&quot;async&quot; src=&quot;https://example.com/eleventy-base-blog/blog/2024-10-02-desk-cleanup/I6UCUSvtsj-4000.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Desk&quot; width=&quot;4000&quot; height=&quot;1800&quot;&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now let&#39;s get real. Soon I will have a bunch of other things (clutter) which will occupy most of the zen like space I have now. But, I will try to keep it like this or at least get into a routine of cleaning it up once a week. Until then, I&#39;ll enjoy the serenity in my room.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>